@content_cozy
I'm holding up by myself on top of this finished melody
Tell me now that its over let me know
In an instant raindrops form near my eyes
You from. Even when i just breathe I see you
Seem like its true that love blooms like a cherry blossom and then easily flods away
It was like I dreamed. We burned like fireworks but only ashes remained
Hey girl I know this is a conclusion that you made on your own
Your hands your body
Your heat that was hotter than the equator is all gone
Since i'm constantly in the same spot of this melody i'm on the repeat sign
Hit the period mark i'm repeating by myself on this written music sheet
I'm holding up by myself on top of this finished melody
Tell me now that its over let me know
Girl let me know girl let me know
Although I know its all over now
That you probably have no feelings left
Girl let me know
Just say anything
I just wanna know
My lingering feelings are holding on in front of the period mark
So just tell me anything girl let me know
The promise we made together
Disappeared somewhere with time
Dominoes that fell due to the strength of a break up
It's like Juliet and Romeo
If I liked you too much
Protecting it between the heat from you and I
I look back onto it now the film between you and I
Oh I gotta need a thoughts of you and
You took away the stars of my night and the sun in my day
In the end there's only
Clouds left in darkness
That's right the rule that there are break ups if there are meetings
Never ever whatever rule that is I want to break it
Look away from it hypnotized by you
I'm holding up by myself on top of this finished melody
Tell me now that it's over let me know
Girl let me know
Although I know its all over now
That you probably have no feelings left
Girl let me know
Just say anything
I just wanna know
My lingering feelings are holding on in front of the period mark
So just tell me anything girl let me know
We're all fools idiots
In hopes of a chance we hold onto a love thats ended already
I don't still have feelings I know that I can't go on too
But sometimes like I can't digest why?
Like I can't digest my insides feel like they're going to explode and it comes up and makes me throw up
In my imagination we fight make up and i understand you
You hand movements your stares have become faint but why won't they disappear
Why won't they disappear? Why?
Why
Girl let me know
Although I know its all over now
That you probably have no feelings left
Girl let me know
Just say anyhing
I just wanna know
My lingering feelings are holding on in front of the period mark
So just tell me anything girl let me know
Let me know